Guide to the Willard Straight Hall records, 1925-2004.
Willard Straight Hall records
- Series XV. Alphabetical Subject Files 1932
  - Activities Committee, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Billiard Room, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Board of Managers, 1932-33 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Boy Scouts, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Foster M Coffin personal, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - CUCA, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Columbia University, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Dance Committee, 1932-33 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Delano and Aldrich, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Dartmouth, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Drake, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Employment, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Form Letters, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Hostess, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Hotel, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Insurance, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Library, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Membership A-L, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Membership M-Z, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Membership Summer Session, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Musicales, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Princeton, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - PDR Accounts, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Supplies A-L, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Supplies M-Z, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Straight News, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - University Unions, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - WSH, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - EA Whiting, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Yale, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence A-XYZ, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 11-33)
- Series XVI. Alphabetical Subject Files 1933-35
  - General Correspondence A, 1933-35 (Box 13, Folder 34-36)
  - Activities Committee, 1933-35 (Box 13, Folder 37-38)
  - General Correspondence B, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 4-6)
  - Billiard Room, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 7-9)
  - Board of Managers, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 10-11)
  - Beer Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Boy Scouts, 1934-35 (Box 14, Folder 13-14)
  - General Correspondence C, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 15-17)
  - Chimemasters, 1934-35 (Box 14, Folder 18-19)
  - Columbia, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 20-22)
  - Country Day School Assn, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 24-26)
  - Foster M Coffin Personal, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 27-29)
  - CUCA, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 30-32)
  - General Correspondence D, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 33-36)
  - Dance Committee, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 37-38)
  - Dining Room Dept, 1934-35 (Box 14, Folder 39-40)
  - Dartmouth, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 41-43)
  - General Correspondence E, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 44-46)
  - Employment, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 47-49)
  - Employees Athletic Club, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - General Correspondence F, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 51-53)
  - General Correspondence G, 1933-35 (Box 14, Folder 54-56)
  - General Correspondence H, 1933-35 (Box 15, Folder 1-3)
  - Hotel, 1933-35 (Box 15, Folder 4-6)
  - Hostess, 1933-35 (Box 15, Folder 7-9)
  - General Correspondence I, 1933-35 (Box 15, Folder 10-12)
  - Insurance, 1933-35 (Box 15, Folder 13-15)
  - General Correspondence J, 1933-35 (Box 15, Folder 16-18)
  - General Correspondence K, 1933-35 (Box 15, Folder 19-21)
  - General Correspondence L, 1933-35 (Box 15, Folder 22-24)
  - Library, 1933-36 (Box 15, Folder 25-27)
  - Lost and Found Dept, 1932, 1934-35 (Box 15, Folder 28-30)
  - General Correspondence M, 1933-35 (Box 15, Folder 31-33)
  - Membership Summer, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Membership, 1933-35 (Box 15, Folder 35-37)
  - Memos, 1932-35 (Box 15, Folder 38-41)
  - Musicales, 1933-35 (Box 15, Folder 42-43)
  - General Correspondence N, 1933-35 (Box 15, Folder 44-46)
  - General Correspondence O, 1933-35 (Box 15, Folder 47-49)
  - Open Road, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - General Correspondence P, 1933-35 (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
  - Placement Bureau, 1934-35 (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
  - Penn State, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania, 1933-35 (Box 16, Folder 7-9)
  - Princeton, 1933-35 (Box 16, Folder 10-12)
  - General Correspondence Q, 1933-35 (Box 16, Folder 13-15)
  - Quill and Dagger, 1934-35 (Box 16, Folder 16-17)
  - General Correspondence R, 1933-35 (Box 16, Folder 18-20)
  - Rotary, 1934-35 (Box 16, Folder 21-22)
  - General Correspondence S, 1933-35 (Box 16, Folder 23-25)
  - Sphinx Head, 1933-35 (Box 16, Folder 26-28)
  - Straight News, 1933-34 (Box 16, Folder 29-30)
  - Summer Session, 1934-35 (Box 16, Folder 31-32)
  - Supplies, 1933-35 (Box 16, Folder 33-38)
  - Syracuse, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - General Correspondence T, 1933-35 (Box 16, Folder 40-42)
  - General Correspondence U, 1933-35 (Box 16, Folder 43-45)
  - University Unions, 1933-34 (Box 16, Folder 46-47)
  - University Unions, 1935 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence V, 1933-35 (Box 17, Folder 2-4)
  - General Correspondence W, 1933-35 (Box 17, Folder 5-7)
  - Whiting, 1933-35 (Box 17, Folder 8-10)
  - Willard Straight Hall, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Yale, 1934-35 (Box 17, Folder 12-13)
  - General Correspondence XYZ, 1933-35 (Box 17, Folder 14-16)
  - Quarterly Bulletin of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen, 1932-44 (Box 17, Folder 17-64)
- 14th Hotel Anniversary, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 65)
- Summer Session, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 66)
- Summer Session, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 67)
- Series XVII. Alphabetical Subject Files 1936
  - General Correspondence A, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Art, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Activities, 1935-36 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Art Correspondence, 1935-36 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - General Correspondence B, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Billiards Room, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Board of Managers, 1935-36 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence C, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - CURW, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence D, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Dance, 1935-36 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Dining Room, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence E, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Employment, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence F, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence G, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence H, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Housekeeper, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Hotel, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence I, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence J, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence K, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence L, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Library, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence M, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Membership, 1936-37 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Memos, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Musicales, 1935-36 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence N, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence O, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence P, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Pennsylvania, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Penn State, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Placement Bureau, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - General Correspondence R, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Social Director, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Straight News, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Supplies A-L, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Supplies M-Z, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Summer Session, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - General Correspondence T, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - General Correspondence U, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - University Unions, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - General Correspondence V, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence W, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Whiting Personal, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence XYZ, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Series XVIII. Alphabetical Subject Files 1937
  - General Correspondence A, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Act. Comm., 1936-37 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Association, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Art Exhibits, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence B, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Barber Shop, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Billiard Room, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Board of Managers, 1936-37 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence C, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Chimemasters, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Columbia, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - C.U.R.W., 1937 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence D, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Dance Committee, 1936-37 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Dartmouth, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Dining Room, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Dr. Day, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence E, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Employees Athletic Club, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Employment, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - General Correspondence F, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - General Correspondence G, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence H, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Hotel, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Hostess, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Housekeeping, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - General Correspondence I, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Insurance, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Inauguration Dr. Day, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - International Association, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Independent Association, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - General Correspondence J, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - General Correspondence K, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - General Correspondence L, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - General Correspondence M, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Membership, 1937-38 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Memos, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Musicales, 1937-38 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence N, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence O, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence P, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Placement Bureau, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Penn State, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Princeton, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence Q, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Quill and Dagger, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence R, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Rotary, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence S, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Sphinx Head, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Supplies A-L, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Supplies M-Z, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Summer Session, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Syracuse, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence T, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence U, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - University Unions, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence V, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence W, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Whiting, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence XYZ, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Yale, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Board of Managers, 1937-38 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Series XIX. Alphabetical Subject Files 1938
  - Board of Managers, 1938-39 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - General Correspondence G, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence H, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Hotel, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Housekeeping, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence I, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - International Association of Ithaca, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Independent Association, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence J, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence K, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence L, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Library, 1937-38 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Library, 1938-39 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence M, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Memos, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Membership, 1938-39 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Musicales, 1938-39 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence N, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence O, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence P, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Princeton, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Pennsylvania, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Penn State, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Placement Bureau, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Public Information, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence R, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence S, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Straight News, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Summer Session, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Supplies A-L, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Supplies M-Z, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - General Correspondence T, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - General Correspondence U, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - University Unions, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence V, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - General Correspondence W, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Whiting, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - WSH Construction, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Yale, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - General Correspondence XYZ, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Series XX. Alphabetical Subject Files 1939-40
  - General Correspondence A, 1939-1940 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Activities Committee, 1939-40 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Addition to WHS, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Art Exhibition, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Art Exhibition Plans, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Art Exhibition Committee, 1939-40 (Box 22, Folder 24-25)
  - Athletic Association, 1939-40 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - General Correspondence B, 1939-40 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Billiard Room, 1939-40 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Board of Managers, 1939-40 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1939-40 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence C, 1939-40 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Cornell Club of Ithaca, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - CURW, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence D, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Dartmouth, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Day, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Dance Committee, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Delano and Aldrich, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Dining Rooms, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence E, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Employment, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Exchange Club, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence F, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence G, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence H, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Hotel, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence I, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Independent Association, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Insurance, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - International Association, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence J, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence K, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence L, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Library, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - General Correspondence M, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Membership, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Memos, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Music (Sunday), 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Music Program, 1939-40 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence N, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - New Furnishings, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence O, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence P, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Public Information, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Princeton, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Penn State, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Placement Bureau, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence R, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence S, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Social Director, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Straight News, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Summer Session, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Summer Session, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Supplies A-L, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Supplies M-Z, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence T, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence U, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - University Unions, 1939
    - University Unions, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Wisconsin Correspondence with Butts, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence with Butts, 1939-40 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania-Houston, 1939-40 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Rochester, 1939-40 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Florida: Correspondence with Matthews, 1939-40 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Colgate: Correspondence with Freeman, 1939-40 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Buffalo: Correspondence with Robert Parke, 1939-40 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota: Correspondence with Higgins, 1939-40 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Iowa: Correspondence with Rehder, 1939-40 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Indiana: Correspondence with Patrick, 1939-40 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Purdue: Correspondence with Valley, 1939-40 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence V, 1939-40 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence W, 1939-40 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Whiting, 1939-40 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence XYZ, 1939-40 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Yale, 1939-40 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Series XXI. Alphabetical Subject Files 1940-41
  - Activities Misc, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Activities Misc, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Art Exhibitions, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Alumni, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Athletic Assn, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Billiard Room, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Barber Shop, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Board of Managers, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Bridge, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Calendars, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Cornell Club of Ithaca, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Cornell Musical Clubs, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Cornell Club of New York, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - C.U.R.W, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Dances, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Dr. Day and Mrs. Day, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Employment, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Graham, 1940-41 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Hotel, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - International Association, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Independent Association, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Insurance, Bonds etc, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Library, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Memos, 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Musicals (Sunday), 1940-41 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Music Program, 1940-41 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Membership, 1940-41 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Placement Bureau, 1940-41 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania, 1940-41 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Princeton, 1940-41 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Penn State, 1940-41 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Public Information, 1940-41 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Social Director, 1940-41 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Student Council, 1940-41 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Summer Session, 1940-41 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Supplies A-L, 1940-41 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Supplies M-Z, 1940-41 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Straight News, 1940-41 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - University Unions, 1940-41 (Box 26, 29, Folder 9, 25)
  - Whiting- Personal, 1940-41 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 1940-41 (Box 28-29, Folder 22-23,1-3,5-12,14-15,20-24,26-27)
- Series XXII. Alphabetical Subject Files 1941-42
  - Activities Misc., 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Misc., 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Art Exhibitions, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Athletic Association, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Bridge, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Barber Shop, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Billiard Room, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Radio Guild, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - C.U.R.W, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Club of NY, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Club of Ithaca, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Dances, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Dining Room, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Dramatic Club, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Employment, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - General Correspondence A-XYZ, 1941-42 (Box 30, Folder 22-33, 39-40, 41-45)
  - Library, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Membership, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Making Democracy Work, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Memos, 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Musicales (Sunday), 1941-42 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Music Program (Carnegie), 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - New Hostess, 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania, 1941-42 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Penn State, 1941-42 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Placement Bureau, 1941-42 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Princeton, 1941-42 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Public Information, 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Reunion, 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Sphinx Head, 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Social Director, 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Social Director- Assistant Applications, 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Social Director and rep, 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Straight News, 1941-42 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Student Council, 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Summer Session, 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Supplies A-L, 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Supplies M-Z, 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - University Unions, 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Whiting- Personal, 1941-42 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Series XXIII. Alphabetical Subject Files 1943-44
  - Alumni Miscellaneous, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - General Correspondence B, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - General Correspondence C, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - General Correspondence D, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - General Correspondence E, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence F, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence G, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - General Correspondence H, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - General Correspondence I, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - General Correspondence J, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - General Correspondence K, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - General Correspondence L, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - General Correspondence M, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - General Correspondence N, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - General Correspondence O, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Office Correspondence, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - General Correspondence R, 1943-44 (Box 31, Folder 41)
- Series XXIV. Alphabetical Subject Files 1946-47
  - General Correspondence A, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Activities Miscellaneous, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence B, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence C, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence D, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence E, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence F, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence G, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence H, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence I, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence J, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence K, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence L, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence M, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence N, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence O, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence P, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence R, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence S, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence T, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence V, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence W, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Willard Straight Hall, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 23)